Guide to the Stanford University, International Development Education Center, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-2005-328
  - Ph.D. Applicants 1976-77 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - John C. Bock, SEA Trip, Summer 1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - S.E.A. Trip, Dean A. Coladarci, March-April 1973 – Manila, Jakarta, Singapore, Kuala Lumpur, Chiang Mai, Hong Kong (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SEA – 1972/73. Did not come and rejected (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - SEA recruiting, 1972-73 – Philippines, Hong Kong (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Thailand (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - SIDEC copies: Bock Correp. SEA trip – Indonesia, Singapore, Malaysia (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - SEA – form letter on biblio. ref. material (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - J. Peter Grace (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Ford/SEA – Correspondence – Ford (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Moore Memo Coladarci, 8/6/70, Report New York and Washington (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Mct. – Ford/SE Asia – 1-CAB-646 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Ford/SE Asia – Faculty Recruitment (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Ford/SE Asia – Student Recruitment (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - China (Hong Kong) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Indonesia (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Korea (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Laos (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Malaysia (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Philippines (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Singapore (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Thailand – Dr. Philip G. Davidson – Ford Found. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Thailand (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Vietnam (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - United States (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - EWA - Contract Negotiations (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Asia Foundation/Korean Seminar Accounting (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Far Horizons – Government guidelines. ACE research grants. USOE program basic research (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Ford – Manila/Peralta/SIDEC Proposal, 7/28/69 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Stanford/Los Andes Draft Proposal, Bogota, Columbia. Oct. 1969 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Ford/LA Applicant File List, 1974-75 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - M.A. Program – welcoming letter, useful information list (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Unfoldered – reimbursements, letters. (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - SU revised expense list 1975-76 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Student Recommendations (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - SEA graduate lists (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Student Funding awards (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Addresses, Southeast Asia (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Applications – research (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Unfoldered – Ford Foundation publications (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Recruitment – Latin American Fellowship Program, 1970-71 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Addresses, UNDP Reps. (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Addresses, Ford Foundations (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Addresses, German (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Visiting Scholars, 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Visiting Scholars – Inquiries (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Visiting Scholars – Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Visiting Scholars and other short-term appointments (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Mark Bray, Visiting Scholar (Weiler/Levin, sponsors) Jan-Apr 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Antonio Canabate, Jose Maria Cabre (Carnoy, sponsor) 7/1-9/30/91 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sam Gopinathan, Singapore, Spring 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Anne Hudson, Australia (Carnoy, sponsor) May/June 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Emma G. Koreysha, Russia (Carnoy, sponsor) 1992/93 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Molly N. N. Lee, Malaysia (Ramirez, sponsor) 1/94-6/94 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Chi-ning Liu, Visiting Scholar (Carnoy/Rohlen, sponsors) May 1991-May 1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Ignacio Llamas, Mexico (Levin/Carnoy, sponsors) 9/92-6/93 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Anjana Mangalagiri, New Delhi (Carnoy, sponsor) 1993/94 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Roberto Moscati, Milano, Italy (Carnoy, sponsor) Spring 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Yasuhiko Nakno, Japan (Cohen/Noddings, sponsors) 3/11/93 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - George Papagiannis, Visiting Scholar, Advisor: Carnoy, 9/1/91-6/30/92 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Vanilda Paiva, Visiting Scholar, May-June 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Hermenegilde Rwantabagu, Potential Visiting Scholar, Summer 1992 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Jerzy Tomala, Visiting Scholar (Carnoy, sponsor) 1989-90 academic year (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Yu, Zheng, Postdoctoral Scholar:China, Advisor: Carnoy (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 20th Anniversary SIDEC, 1-CAA-101 OPEN (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 20th Anniversary SIDEC, 1-CAA-101 1985 CLOSED (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Freire Workshop, back-up material 1-CAA-101 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Freire Workshop, Expenditures, 1-CAA-101 CLOSED (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Freire Workshop, Corresp. and Budget, 1-CAA-101 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Ford Foundation – West Africa, final report: Grant no. 810-0871 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Francophone Grant 1-CAB662 OPEN (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Diame, Bakary, Francophone Grant (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Nson, Henri, Francophone Grant 1983-84 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Ford Foundation, Weiler, 1-CAB-662 CLOSED 1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Ford Foundation, Weiler, 1-CAB-662 CLOSED 1985 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Swedish Grant (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - USIA/Sweden Grant, Contract (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - U515 Sweden, CIES (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Swedish Proposal (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - SIDEC – Stockholm Project (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Sweden – June 1984 trip (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Sweden grant 1983-84 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Untitled – receipts, bills, financial stuff, UNESCO (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - UNESCO account 1-CDC-933 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Malaysia Program 1987, 1-CDZ-904 CLOSED (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - 1-CDZ-904 OPEN (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Grant, H. Weiler, 2-PDZ-622, CRIS (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Long Range Planning 1977 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Long Range Planning, Campbell and 40614 questionnaires (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Long Range Planning, SIDEC Doctoral Program questionnaire (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Long Range Planning, Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Long Range Planning – Rationale for SIDEC Program (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - SIDEC questionnaire 1977 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Long Range Planning Questionnaires – Completed (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ford Foundation 1981 Recruitment Package – cc of all letters sent (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - SIDEC - Francophone West Africa Program Proposal (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Recruitment Trip West Africa, Nov. 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Recruitment Trip West Africa, March 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Recruitment Package, Francophone WA – letter, March 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - SIDEC world responses (Spring 1992) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - SIDEC world 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - SIDEC Newsletter – materials for future editions (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1981 Memo on Ford Foundation Francophone Program – English (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1981 Memo on Ford Foundation Francophone Program – French (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Memo on Francophone Fellowship – English version – OLD (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Memo on Francophone Fellowship – French version – OLD (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ford Foundation Proposal 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Proposal, Francophone W.A. Research Training Prog. June 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - SIDEC Francophone W. African Program, Proposal (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - SIDEC Conference travel expenses (Ford Foundation) 1-CAB-664-OPEN (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1-CAB-662 1984 CLOSED (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Ford Foundation – SIDEC, Carnoy, 1-CAB-655 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation W. African Grant 1-CAB662 CLOSED (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation Grant 1-CAB662 – Award letters and Budgets (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Ford Foundation Fellowship Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Akoulouze, Richard, Francophone Grant (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Coulibaly, Medjomo, Francophone Grant (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Diakite, Soumalia, Francophone Grant (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Msangi, Namkari, Francophone Grant 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Parajuli, Pramod (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Seya/Tounkara/Maiga Trip 3/83 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Hans Weiler, Abidjan Project 1983 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Cameroun - Francophone Grant (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Ivory Coast - Francophone Grant (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Mali - Francophone Grant (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Senegal - Francophone Grant (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Ford Foundation Transitional 720-0217, 7-PDZ682 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - African Studies, Money for Francophone prog. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Visiting Professor (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Distinguished International Professorship (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence 1986 – Visiting Scholars (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Visiting Scholar (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Klein, George S. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Untitled – Correspondence of Dr. Henry D'Souza (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Visiting Scholar applications 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Visiting Scholars Inquiries 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Visiting Scholars Inquiries 1982-83 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Visiting Scholars 1981-82 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Juan-Luis Adrados, Visiting Scholar (Sociology) (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Akivaga, S. Kichamu – Visiting Scholar Application (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Eduardo Aponte, Visiting Scholar Fall 1985 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Maria M. Malta Campos, Visiting Scholar (Carnoy, sponsor) Jan.-Mar. 1987 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Herlinda Cancino, Visiting Professor (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Dr. Chuenyane, Visiting Scholar (LaFramboise.Samoff, sponsors) 8/31/87-8/31/88 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - David Court, Dec. 1988 (Carnoy/Weiler) (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Antonio Ospina Cubillos, Visiting Scholar, 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Ramesh Chander Datta, Visiting Scholar 1989-90, (Carnoy, sponsor) (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Udai Desai, Visiting Professor applicant 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Visiting Scholar Henri Dieuzeide 1981/82 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Scholar Betty Jo Dorsey, Academic Year 1989- (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Carlos Alberto Emediato Dec. 86-December 87, M. Carnoy Sponsor (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Moacyr Gadotti, Visiting Professor (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Jose Luis Garcia Garrido, sponsors: Ramirez & Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Visiting Scholar Dr. Aldemir Gracelli, 1982-83 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Gyarmati, Gabriel K. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Visiting Scholar James J. Harpstrite, January-July '87, Sponsor: Grossman (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Visiting Scholar Ruth Hayhoe, 12/1/87-1/15/88 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Jurgen Henze, Visiting Scholar, Spring Quarter 1990, Advisor: Hans Weiler (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Yaacov Iram, Visiting Scholar, Winter Quarter 87-88, Carnoy – Sponsor (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Charles Pierre Jacques, Visiting Scholar, 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Flores, Castro (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Kato, Tetsuro, Visiting Scholar, Political Sci., 9/1/86-1/31/87 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Deidre Kelly, Visiting Scholar; W, Sp, S 1991; Sponsor: Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Sarfraz Khawaja, Visiting Scholar Applicant (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Pablo Latapi, Visiting Scholar, Fall 1987 (Weiler) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Claudia Lecaros, Visiting Scholar, Summer 1990, Sponsor: Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Gero Lenhardt, Visiting Professor, Winter Quarter 1985/86 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Yin-Ching Leong, Visiting Scholar, 1987-88, Weiler (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Visiting Scholar T. L. Maliyamkono, Jan-Jun 1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Enguita Mariano, Visiting Scholar, 1984-85 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Visiting Scholar, T. Marimuthu, 1982/3 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - T. Marimuthu, Visiting Scholar, Oct-July 1987-88, Weiler/Cohen (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Dr. Martin de la Rosa Medellin (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Visiting Scholar Ruth E. Meena, 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Erroll Miller, Visiting Scholar, Weiler/Carnoy, May-August 1988 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Ferenc Miszlivetz – Center for European Studies (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Jean J. Moisset, Visiting Scholar, 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Morose, Joseph, Visiting Scholar, 1984-85 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Birgit Negussie, Visiting Scholar? (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Bertilio J. Nery B., Visitor Fall Quarter 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Pius Ng'wandu, Visiting Scholar, 1/87-3/87, Samoff (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Curriculum Vitae, Michael Paige (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Frances Payne, Visiting Scholar, 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Gerard Postiglione, Visiting Scholar ?, 9/87, Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Majid Rahnema, Visiting Scholar, Fall Quarter 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Gosta Rehn, April 1, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - William M. Rideout, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Lawrence J. Saha, Visiting Scholar, Fall 1988-, Ramirez (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Committee on German Professorship In Comparative Western European Studies: Manfred Schmidt, Visiting Professor (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Teresa Selame, Visiting Scholar, New Policy Center, 1986-87 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Princy H. Siriwardene (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Nelly Stromquist, Visiting Scholar, July 1 1985-August 1 1986 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Ronald Sultana, U Malta, Apr-June 1990, Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Judith Torney-Purta, Visiting Scholar, Winter and Spring 1991, Weiler (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Rodolfo torres, Visiting Scholar, Spring 1989, Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Elena Viveros Jarry, Visiting Scholar, Dec 1986-Dec 1987, Levin? (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Hans Peter Widmaier, 5/1/91-7/31/91, Carnoy/Weiler (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Carolyn Winter, Visiting Scholar, 1/87, Carnoy/Levine (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Rong Yilun, Visiting Scholar, 1983-84 AY (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Qui, Yuan, Visiting Scholar, 5/6-31/84, 1983-84 AY (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Wu Zonglan, Visiting Scholar, 1988-89, Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Fetterman, David, Student evaluation (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Mr. Ranyobo Jonas Monaisa, South Africa, Carnoy (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - SIDEC-sponsored activities (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Staff- SIDEC (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - SIDEC Student Association (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Schools and the World Project (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Samoff – Memoranda (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Richard Valencia, Post-Doctoral Fellow, Summer 1982-83 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Philip Fletcher, Post-Doctoral Fellow, 1983-84 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Post-Doctoral Fellows (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Post-Doctoral Fellows, 1982-83, Inquiries (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Lists – Misc. Students (SUSE) – Latin American, SE Asian (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - SIDEC M.A. Graduates (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Lists- MA program (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Lists – PhD program (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Ph.D. Graduates (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - David Nti Memorial Fund 1983 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Faculty Search for Weiler replacement in SIDEC 1988/89 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Paul Hanna (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Kallaway, Peter (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Francis Method, Distinguished Visiting Practitioner, Fall Quarter, 1988-89 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Isidoro Cheresky, Visiting Scholar, Winter/Spring 1990 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - SIDEC/CIES 20th Anniversary Conference, Apr 15-20, 1985, Original Letters (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - SIDEC 20th Anniversary and CIES Conference (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - SIDEC World, Fall 1989 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - SIDEC World Summer 1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - SIDEC Newsletter 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - SIDEC – Medium term plans: "Relfections on the Past and Plans for the Future" Weiler 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - SIDEC Graduation Ceremonies (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - SIDEC – One year temporary faculty position (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - SIDEC – Proposed Plans and changes (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Report, SIDEC (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - SIDEC Winter retreat, Feb 19, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - SIDEC Study committee reports: Center, Res. Colloq., undergrad., MA, symp. 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - SIDEC retreat, Fall 1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - SIDEC retreat, Sept. 21, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - SIDEC Search (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Stromquist (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Professor Zainal Ghani, Malaysia, Summer 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Philip G. Altbach, Visiting Professor, Winter and Spring Quarters 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Robert A. Arnove – Curriculum Vitae (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - de Rebello, Daphne (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Statistics: SIDEC, Applications, Admissions, and Enrollments (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Statistics: SIDEC Admissions/Faculty Load (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - SIDEC Student Concerns (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - SIDEC Faculty search 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - South African Study Program (proposed) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Southeast Program, Summer 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Malaysia Program 1987 – social events and trips (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Malaysia Program 1987 – Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Malaysia Program 1987 – Proposal (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Malaysia Program 1987 – Schedule (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Shipping information (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Malaysia Program 1987 – List of participants (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Malaysia Program 1987 – Meeting Minutes (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Malaysian Program – Housing and Meals (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Unfoldered – Special Workshop on Educational Development and Management for the Ministry of Education, Malaysia. Stanford University, June 21-Aug 16 1987 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - UNESCO Conference – contract, 1CDC933 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Symposium Summary (Stanford/UNESCO) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Background Paper (draft) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - For Your Signature (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - UNESCO Conference – regrets (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Stanford/UNESCO Symposium – Invitations, Mar 1986 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - UNESCO Conference, Resource Accept (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Invitation Lists (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - UNESCO Conference, Observers Accept (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - UNESCO Conference, Participants Accept (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Funding (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - CIES National Conference, Apr 16-20, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - CIES Western Regional Meeting, Nov 9-10, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Western Reg. Conf. of the Comparative and International Education Soc CIES 1983 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - CIES Conference – Discussants (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Unfoldered – CIES Membership Forms (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - CIES – Abstracts of Papers (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - CIES conference – announcement and call for papers (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - CIES – Budget (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - CIES Conference Back-up Material, 1-CAA-101 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - CIES Conference Budget Statements, 1-CAA-101 CLOSED (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - CIES Conference, Back-Up Material, 1-CAA-208 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - CIES Conference Budget Statements, 1-CAA-208 CLOSED (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - CIES Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - CIES Ditto Masters (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Final Program information (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - CIES Conference – Housing (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - CIES Conference – Memoranda (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - CIES Conference – Notes from Meetings (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - CIES – Program List (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - CIES – Proposal Ratings (completed) (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - CIES – Requests for Announcements (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - CIES Conference – Room reservations (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Western Regional Conference of the Comparative and International Education (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - CIES – Preliminary Program (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - CIES – Final program (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - CIES – Registrants (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Untitled – speech (Carnoy), lecture (Amadou-Mahtar M'Bow), paper (Husen) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Untitled – memorandum, Intnat'l Dev. Research Center (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Untitled - SIDEC conference workshop notes, Apr 17, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hans Weiler, Richard Maclure (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Untitled – SIDEC 20th Anniv. Conf. Apr 16-20, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Untitled – SIDEC 20th Anniv. Conf. Apr 16-20, workshop review paper (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - David Fetterman (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - John Hoffmire (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Roberta Fleischman (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Shirley Heath, Lois Harmon (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Untitled - Edmundo Fuenzalida (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Joel Samoff, Jeff Unsicker (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Grant Lewis, Casanueva (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1987 Proposal USIA (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - USAID (proposal) 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - AID proposal (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Unfoldered –Many many sheets of paper (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - USAID proposal, July 1983 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Freire Workshop Mailing List 1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Freire Workshop Stanford Applicants 1983 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Freire Workshop non-SUSE Applicants 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Freire Workshop syllabus originals (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Freire Workshop accounting info 1983 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Freire Workshop participant list 1983 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Freire Workshop correspondenc 1983 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Unfoldered – Misc Freire media (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Francophone West Africa Program (FWA) – Advising (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - FWA Bibl (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - FWA SUSE internal (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - FWA students (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - FWA corresp. R. Harbison 10/77- (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - FWA corresp. R. Harbison through 9/77 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - FWA – workshop Bamako, April 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - FWA – meeting Dakar February 1978 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - FWA – program documents (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - FWA – Senegal (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - FWA – Mali (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - FWA Report (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - FWA – closing out 1987 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Ford/FWA – third grant 1981 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Revision FWA announcement 1981/82 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Financial Aid – M. Coulibaly and R. Akoulouze (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - FWA – Budget, grant, etc. (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - TA Position – Francophone grant April 1982 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Lagos – Nov. 1981 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - FWA - AID (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Filing - FWA (Box 12, Folder 47)